http://www.uwgb.edu/directory/privacy-policy/

Your Phoenix Story Starts Now
Let us help you write a story that includes outstanding programs, award-winning professors, friends for life and the career you want.
Discover UW-Green Bay (pdf)
Academics
Undecided?
You're not alone! Explore our many programs and contact Academic Advising for help.
Admissions
Questions about college?
We can answer questions about applying, majors, campus life, housing and so much more. Let us help!
Getting Started
At UW-Green Bay, students experience hands-on learning from award-winning faculty on a naturally beautiful campus. Learn more about academics, campus life, affordability, and how to apply.
Visit
Apply
Athletics
See You At The Game
D-I athletics offers a chance to be part of something big... from events like Homecoming to student orgs like the Green Bandana Brigade.
View Events
Support Your Team
Green Bay Phoenix
Manitowoc Blue Devils
Marinette Buccaneers
Sheboygan Wombats
Division 1 Men's
Basketball
Faculty & Staff
Looking for someone?
Use the directory to find a faculty or staff member, or search for an office location.
Search Directory
Employee Resources
Human Resources
Provost
Grants & Research
Institutional Strategy & Effectiveness
Employee Wellness
SOFAS
Navigate
Need Help?
Password Reset
Technology Support
Submit News
Academic Calendar
Administrative Calendar
Students
Get Involved!
With 130 student orgs and more than 1,000 events, there's always something to do on campus.
View Events Calendar
The Phoenix Lifestyle
Campus Events
Dining
Intramurals
Student Orgs
Student Government
Pride Center
Privacy Policy
State of Wisconsin laws exist to ensure that government is open and that the public has a right to access appropriate records and information possessed by state government. At the same time, there are exceptions to the public's right to access public records provided by both state and federal laws. These exceptions include the privacy of individuals.
Information collected at this site becomes public record and may be subject to inspection and copying by the public, unless an exception in law exists. During your visit to the University of Wisconsin-Green Bay’s website, information that is not readily identifiable to an individual is automatically collected and stored. This information is used solely to improve our web services. For more detail on our privacy policy, please see the expanded statement following.
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which the University of Wisconsin-Green Bay collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://www.uwgb.edu website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by the University of Wisconsin-Green Bay.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non- personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer, mobile device, or other device you use to access our Site, and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. We use this information in an aggregate fashion to track access to uwgb.edu. At no time do we disclose site usage by individual IP addresses. Web server logs are retained on a temporary basis and then deleted from our systems.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
How we use collected information
The University of Wisconsin-Green Bay may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
To improve customer service
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
To personalize user experience
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
To improve our Site
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other Site feature
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
To send periodic emails
We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.
Third party websites
Users may find content on our Site that links to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.
Changes to this privacy policy
The University of Wisconsin-Green Bay has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
UW-Green Bay Web Services Office
Address:
Web Services Office IS 1148 - COMPUTING University of Wisconsin-Green Bay
This document was last updated on January 10, 2013.
